# IZUCHUKWU (IZU) NJOKU

Winnipeg, Manitoba R3T 2K1| 204.230.2253

<u>zuic5527@gmail.com</u>| Portfolio: <a href="https://izuchukn.github.io/zuicart.github.io/Portfolio/">https://izuchukn.github.io/zuicart.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

# CAREER SUMMARY

A Bachelor of Fine Arts Final year student with three years of experience in Digital Art. An
animator experienced in 3-D modeling, rendering, 2-D animation, sound engineering and video editing who
has a passion for various forms of art.

# AREAS OF PROFICIENCY

- Graphic Design
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Blender (3-D animation software)
- DaVinci Resolve (Professional editing software), Final Cut pro.
- 2-D animation

- Sound Engineering
- Painting and Drawing
- Leadership and People Skills.
- Microsoft Office

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **GRACE DIGITAL PRODUCTION, Winnipeg, Manitoba**

November 2020-Present

#### 3D Animator and Content Director

- Outsourced and managed Freelance Script writers for videos aired on the Organizations YouTube channel.
- Created thumbnail pictures for YouTube videos using 3D and 2D animation.
- Worked directly with the owner of organization on a 3D animation video project.
- Created videos with effect and text for audio recording featured on their YouTube Channel.
- Ensuring video and effect is consistent with the message of the brand.

**Skilled gained:** Blender, Adobe Illustrator, Sound Engineering, Graphic design, 2-D animation, Leadership, People Skills.

# ANIMATOR AND SOUND ENGINEER (Freelance), Winnipeg, Manitoba August 2017 - Present

- Created various soundtracks for individuals with needs varying from music production to movie production.
- Helped designed logos, motion graphic videos and flyers for individuals to promote their brand.
- Promoting personal brand and social media (Instagram: @zuiccy)
   Skilled gained: Blender, Adobe Illustrator, Sound Engineering, Graphic design, 2-D animation.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Fine Arts (Studio)**

January 2016 - June 2021

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Manitoba